http://www.decaljunky.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Decal Junky will never use your name, address, phone number or email address for anything other than business with Decal Junky. We may use your name, email address and location to target ads in an effort to advertise new products and specials that we may be running. This will be done through our ad campaigns that run on websites that display our ads.
Furthermore, we will never sell or rent any of the above information to anyone. We want you to feel comfortable and secure when doing business with us. Be assured that the information that you provide when ordering a product is secure and protected. If you feel more comfortable ordering by regular mail, please follow the steps outlined in the Mail Order Process posted on the customer service page.
What we need to collect
We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special categories of information or location-based information. This does, however, include name, address, email etc. We collect only the data that is necessary for us to contract with you when you purchase goods or services from us. Our company will be what is known as the Controller of the personal data you provide to us.
Why we need it
We need to collect data that is for us to process an online payment, to deliver your purchased product and to meet our statutory reporting obligations. In such cases, we don’t need to get your consent (since we can fulfill our contract without the data) but we still want you to know how carefully we manage the protection of that data. We will not collect any personal data from you that we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you.
What we do with it
All the personal data we process is processed by our staff, and, for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance, this information is located on servers that are covered by the Privacy Shield. We will only share your data with third parties where legally required to do so. We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. Our online store allows our administrators to anonymize and delete your personal data in a timely and responsible manner and also allows you to request the immediate deletion of your data once the transaction is full and final and we have met our statutory reporting obligations. You will find an option to delete the data on your account page. (You will not be able to delete data where we have an overriding obligation to retain it.)How long we keep it
We have formal retention which requires us to keep details of your transactions for a period of six years from the date of the transaction in order to meet our statutory reporting obligations in respect of our formal accounts as well as in terms of tax reporting. After that point, your data will be deleted.
What we would also like to do with it
We would like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar products. This is a legitimate purpose allowed for in law; this information is not shared with third parties and you can unsubscribe at any time.
What are your rights?
If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information, you can object to its use and even have it corrected or deleted. In order to exercise these rights, or if you wish to raise a complaint about how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Officer who will investigate the matter.
If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the relevant supervisory authority.
×
